

Rus Narcisa

22N Uruşagului St., Floreşti, Romania + 40 740 94 98 99 | rusnarcisa16@gmail.com Date of birth: Nov 16th, 1984

COO and **General Ledger Accountant** with over 10 years of progressive experience in financial, accounting, administration and HR fields in one of the major companies leading the field in electrical installation and green energy solutions. Proven ability and enjoyment of handling details, making sure that daily operations are done properly, on time and economically. **Areas of experience include:**

- Operations management
- Management of resources
- Implementation of new systems
- Development of existing systems
- Development of new employees
- Team Building & Leadership

EXPERIENCE

2011 – Present

COO, General Ledger Accountant

SC ELECTROPLUS SRL

Hired to create and develop new departments for the company, implement efficient systems and make sure business operations flow smoothly and efficient.

- Created Finance & Accounting Department
- Created Procurement Department
- Created Administration Department
- Created Fleet Manager Role

2014 – Present (Part-Time)

COO, General Ledger Accountant

SC SOFT TECH PLUS SRL

Due to my proven experience in Electroplus srl, I have received the proposal to be part of the process of founding a new company and to occupy the above-listed positions. I accepted the challenge, seeing it as a good opportunity to expand my knowledge.

- Created efficient working systems
- Learned how a software company works

I have launched this company with great enthusiasm with my husband, willing to bring something new to the market.

- Created efficient systems in the company
- Worked with a new account software
- Learned accounting for a manufacturing business
- Grasp a good knowledge about all the manufacturing process

2006 – 2011 Accountant SC ELECTROPLUS SRL

Hired as a primary accountant in the first years of the company, took a great responsibility of assuming step by step the obligations from the collaborating accounting company.

- I provided real time information for the company, which led to the prompt resolution of all important situations that occurred
- I took step by step many tasks from the accounting company, attributions that added value to my professional knowledge
- We had positive feedback from suppliers and customers, which led to the CEO's proposal to quit
 the collaboration with the accounting company and I took over the financial accounting
- I was promoted as a COO and General Ledger Accountant

EDUCATION

2007 – 2008	Bogdan Voda University, Faculty of Economics Master's degree in Management In Administration, Credit Institutions and Companies Cluj-Napoca
2003 – 2007	Bogdan Voda University, Faculty of Economics B.A. in Finance and Banks Cluj-Napoca
1999 – 2003	High School – Didactica Nova Economic College Commercial & Financial Activities Cluj-Napoca

CERTIFICATIONS

May 2011 – Sept. 2011 HR Inspector

Professional Qualification Certificate – Ministry of Education and Research

License F no. 0014663 / 20.09.2011

Sept. 2005 – Nov. 2005 German language certificate – Level 1 - beginner

Certificate of Completion – Britania Language School

License no. 1196 / 22.11.2005

2003 – 2003 Technician in financial and commercial activities

Professional Skills Certificate – Ministry of Education and Research

License A no. 0187185 / 30.09.2005

SKILLS

IT: WinMENTOR - accounting and management software

B-logic Business Software - accounting and management software

CIEL - accounting software

Saga C - accounting software for production businesses

Microsoft Office

Other: Business development, Accounting, Economics, Management, Leadership,

Team work

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Languages: English - beginner

Italian - intermediate German - beginner

Driver license cat: B

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Apr. 2017 Volunteer at CERT

"CERT Prinde Radacini editia 5. Actiune de impadurire Hoia-Suceagu"

Dec. 2014 Volunteer at CERT

"CERT - Umanitara de Craciun"

Apr. 2014 Volunteer at CERT

"CERT Prinde Radacini editia 4. Actiune de impadurire Baisoara"